Don't
别
Your eyes
你的眼睛
Dyson
戴森
David Turner seeds
大卫·特纳 种子
I'm going to get it on my fingers
我要拿到它
I think I can do this
我想我能做到
Not sure what I should do here
不知道我应该在这里做什么
The Scissor everywhere
到处都是剪刀
I'm going to cut I did see a tool that I could use to big
我要切开，我确实看到了可以用来放大的工具
Standard issue
标准问题
There's still some season here that's alright
这里还有些季节还可以
Just enough so you don't choke one of my specialties
恰到好处，您就不会cho我的专业之一
A more elegant way
更优雅的方式
How to deseed a pepper
如何去籽辣椒
Who's the first cut off the stem
谁是第一个切断茎的人
Cut your paper in half
切成两半
So that you can open it right up this fibre and out
这样您就可以在光纤上将其打开
Play some mirror
玩镜子
Cutting into strips
切成条
And then take those strips and cut down
然后把那些条切下来
I just need it so see you not going down
我只需要它，所以看你不会失望
How's the baddest
最糟糕的是
So we're going to deseed a jalapeno and I find the easiest way is the actually
因此，我们将制作墨西哥胡椒，我发现最简单的方法是
Take one side off of the jalapeno
从墨西哥胡椒中取出一侧
And take the next side
再往下切
One more time
再一次
That was behind the scenes with her heart you always have better
她的内心总是在幕后，你总是更好
Stop with your cutting if you leave the skin side of the healthy
如果您离开健康人的皮肤一侧，请停止切割
Facing the board as opposed to facing up
面对板而不是朝上
The first thing I'm going to do is take these ribs out which is the lighter colour pack
我要做的第一件事是将这些肋条取出，这是较浅的颜色包
Come in with my knife sideways
侧着我的刀进来
And just slide right through
然后向右滑动
What are the ribs removed
什么肋骨被删除
My First Cut is When We Collide Julianne which is the longest river
我的第一个切入点是当我们碰撞朱利安纳河时，这是最长的河流
By Juliana
Come back across
回来对面
Daiso juliennes into cubes
大创辣椒切成方块
I felt like a culinary phone
我感觉就像是烹饪电话
Music
Gangster music
Fresh produce
新鲜农产品